<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>USA Online Mills</title>
	<atom:link href="/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 18:23:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Bayern Munich to repay $268,000 for breaking minimum wage rules</title>
		<link>/bayern-munich-to-repay-268000-for-breaking-minimum-wage-rules/</link>
					<comments>/bayern-munich-to-repay-268000-for-breaking-minimum-wage-rules/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[shawon]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 18:23:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1068</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bayern Munich have been forced to repay over 200,000 euros ($216,560) for failing to meet minimum wage requirements over a five-year period, Bavarian customs authorities announced on Thursday. The club must also pay approximately 45,000 euros ($48,700) in unpaid social security contributions. The investigation found Bayern underpaid employees from 2016 to 2021.&#160; The Munich customs ... <a title="Bayern Munich to repay $268,000 for breaking minimum wage rules" class="read-more" href="/bayern-munich-to-repay-268000-for-breaking-minimum-wage-rules/" aria-label="More on Bayern Munich to repay $268,000 for breaking minimum wage rules">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Bayern Munich have been forced to repay over 200,000 euros ($216,560) for failing to meet minimum wage requirements over a five-year period, Bavarian customs authorities announced on Thursday.</p>



<p>The club must also pay approximately 45,000 euros ($48,700) in unpaid social security contributions.</p>



<p>The investigation found Bayern underpaid employees from 2016 to 2021.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The Munich customs office issued a statement on Thursday saying Bayern had employed workers, mostly in the club&#8217;s youth training centre, on limited hours contracts, but &#8220;the actual level of employment was far higher.&#8221;</p>



<p>&#8220;The club did not pay the minimum wage at the youth training centre it operates&#8221; the office said in a statement.&nbsp;</p>



<p>In a press release on Thursday, Bayern apologised for the incident, saying &#8220;it was never FC Bayern Munich&#8217;s intention to withhold employees from their legitimate wages.&#8221;</p>



<p>Bayern said it has cooperated fully with the investigation and has taken steps to ensure similar incidents cannot happen again.&nbsp;</p>



<p>&#8220;The club has cooperated with the process and the procedure is now closed&#8221; Munich customs spokesman Thomas Meister told German news service SID, an AFP subsidiary.&nbsp;</p>



<p>With annual turnover in excess of 650 million euros ($700 million), Bayern is the largest sports club in Germany and the third highest-earning football club in the world, after Real Madrid and Barcelona.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Bayern Munich&#8217;s men&#8217;s team won their 11th straight Bundesliga title in 2022-23, alongside their female counterparts, who have won two of the past three Frauen Bundesliga titles.&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/bayern-munich-to-repay-268000-for-breaking-minimum-wage-rules/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chinese superfan rejoices as Messi visits Beijing</title>
		<link>/chinese-superfan-rejoices-as-messi-visits-beijing/</link>
					<comments>/chinese-superfan-rejoices-as-messi-visits-beijing/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[shawon]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 18:20:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1063</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[BEIJING, June 15 (Reuters) &#8211; For thirtysomething Zhang Jiao, after realising her dream of witnessing Argentina soccer great Lionel Messi lift the World Cup every match he plays from now on is &#8220;precious&#8221;. Zhang travelled from Shanghai to Beijing this week to join scores of other giddy Messi fans as the Argentina captain came to ... <a title="Chinese superfan rejoices as Messi visits Beijing" class="read-more" href="/chinese-superfan-rejoices-as-messi-visits-beijing/" aria-label="More on Chinese superfan rejoices as Messi visits Beijing">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>BEIJING, June 15 (Reuters) &#8211; For thirtysomething Zhang Jiao, after realising her dream of witnessing Argentina soccer great Lionel Messi lift the World Cup every match he plays from now on is &#8220;precious&#8221;.</p>



<p>Zhang travelled from Shanghai to Beijing this week to join scores of other giddy Messi fans as the Argentina captain came to town to play a friendly against Australia.</p>



<p>&#8220;For Messi fans, you really have to cherish the remaining time,&#8221; said Zhang, who was still trying to get a ticket for Thursday&#8217;s game.</p>



<p>&#8220;It is just a friendly game, so there is not much competitive value in it. So why should I come to Beijing this time? But any opportunity to come here, to see him in a game, is valuable, precious, because you know there are not that many left.&#8221;</p>



<p>Not initially a soccer fan, Zhang was hooked at first sight in her Shanghai university dorm when she watched Messi make his World Cup debut as a teenager in 2006.</p>



<p>During the course of Messi&#8217;s glittering career she has watched hundreds of his matches on TV, often getting up in the middle of the night to see him play for Barcelona or Paris St Germain.</p>



<p>Zhang has travelled to Messi&#8217;s hometown in Argentina and to the last three World Cups to see him play.</p>



<p>She visited a monastery in Tibet ahead of the last year&#8217;s tournament to pray for her biggest wish to come true, for Argentina to win in Qatar.</p>



<p>And she watched all seven of his matches from the stands in Qatar, culminating in Argentina&#8217;s victory over France in the final.</p>



<p><strong>[1/5]&nbsp;</strong>Zhang Jiao, a fan of soccer player Lionel Messi, poses near a World Cup trophy replica at a post office selling Argentina football merchandise in Beijing, China June 14, 2023. REUTERS/Florence Lo</p>



<p>&#8220;The feeling was then I no longer had any regrets in my life,&#8221; she said.</p>



<p>&#8220;It was definitely the highlight of my life after so many years, because not only I realised my dream, Messi also realized the dream. So I witnessed this double dream.&#8221;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">WELCOME DISTRACTION</h2>



<p>As she sat on the touchline of an artificial pitch surrounded by dozens of other Chinese fans sporting Argentina shirts having a kickabout, Zhang reflected on the importance of her Messi fandom to her life.</p>



<p>It had allowed her to travel the world, meet people, make friends, share experiences she would not have otherwise had and, she felt, become a more positive person.</p>



<p>It had also proved a welcome distraction from the notoriously long hours demanded of Chinese employees in her jobs at a management consultancy and internet companies.</p>



<p>&#8220;It will make you feel that, in fact, life is actually still very good after all,&#8221; she said, tears filling her eyes.</p>



<p>&#8220;I find Messi can give you a kind of power &#8230; I may have had a very annoying, frustrating or bad time at work, but at least at that time you will feel that you still have something that you love.&#8221;</p>



<p>Messi, at 35, is approaching the twilight of his career as he prepares to move to Inter Miami in the United States and Zhang hopes he will play on for as long as possible, even if she doubts he will be at the 2026 World Cup.</p>



<p>&#8220;One day he will retire, and I can only say that on that day, I can only slowly think back to his long years of playing football, which brought me so much happiness, so many happy moments, I will be especially grateful to him,&#8221; she said.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/chinese-superfan-rejoices-as-messi-visits-beijing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stuart Broad vs David Warner, the Last Aussie standing</title>
		<link>/stuart-broad-vs-david-warner-the-last-aussie-standing/</link>
					<comments>/stuart-broad-vs-david-warner-the-last-aussie-standing/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[shawon]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 18:10:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1050</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[For 19 masochistic innings, over a decade, David Warner has walked out to bat in India to eke out 414 unconvincing runs. For 25 Test innings in England, he averages 26.04. Just regression, not progression. The Australian fans might rate Warner high based on what he has done back home, but for many in the ... <a title="Stuart Broad vs David Warner, the Last Aussie standing" class="read-more" href="/stuart-broad-vs-david-warner-the-last-aussie-standing/" aria-label="More on Stuart Broad vs David Warner, the Last Aussie standing">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>For 19 masochistic innings, over a decade, David Warner has walked out to bat in India to eke out 414 unconvincing runs. For 25 Test innings in England, he averages 26.04. Just regression, not progression. The Australian fans might rate Warner high based on what he has done back home, but for many in the cricketing world, Warner the Test batsman doesn’t trigger much reverence. He will now get his last chance to sparkle in Ashes but will have to move past the big hurdle Stuart Broad from round the stumps. Ben Stokes had talked about how he wanted a really pace bowler, but in the end he picked Broad, no doubt to harass Warner.</p>



<p>Somewhere down the line, Warner has seemingly lost the confidence to attack in Tests. Will he change in what could be his last couple of chances in England? If he fails in the first two Tests, he might well be dropped for good. Forget in India, the reticence to attack has plagued Warner even elsewhere in the past. So much so that his mentors have had to remind him of his own aggressive talent.</p>



<p>At the start of the 2013-14 season, after a fallow run in which he failed to reach a hundred in 23 innings, Trent Woodhill, a renowned batting coach, took Warner to a café in Sydney for a chat about exactly this tendency. The crux of that talk was – ‘Attack the balls there to be hit and defence would look after itself.”</p>



<p>Apparently, so the story goes, that the then coach Mickey Arthur had wanted Warner to strengthen his defense, triggering a mini-slump. In Woodhill’s telling, Warner the batsman is a different beast at the crease once he starts thinking about attacking. He turns busy, the footwork turns more like a boxer’s and he is ready to punch. This tuk-tuk business of being caught stuck at the crease is the worst disservice he can do to himself, and to Australia.</p>



<p>In some ways, David Warner seems to be the last Aussie standing. In respect to the stereotypical version of an Aussie batsman’s technique, for some of us from an earlier generation. Lot more arms, a sense of compactness, preference for punchy shots, boxer’s rapid foot movement in stance to the pacers, the horizontal strokes, the on-the-up salvos, and the sudden deceleration to soft-handed tip-and-runs. Above all, the arms in the shot production. In those aspects, Warner is the last Aussie left. Techniques worldwide are coalescing so much these days that the hitherto uniqueness is fading out gradually. Warner is still a throwback, though.</p>



<p>This is intended to be a piece about his batting; his off-field issues have been well-documented, but just one episode is worth reiterating. Long before the ball tampering or the Joe Root punch, there was an episode at Brisbane’s Centre of Excellence when he was thrown out for attitude issues. This time around, his brother came to his help with an ultimatum. “I’m a plumber, and I said to him, ‘You can give it away and come labour for me, digging trenches, or you can put your head down and put everything into this if you want to be a professional sportsman’,” Steve, his brother, has said in the past. Luckily, Warner did.</p>



<p>The world cricket nearly didn’t have him. When he was 13, Warner was told by his coach to switch to right-hand as he was hitting the ball too much in the air but a season later, with the backing of his mother Lorraine, Warner made the crucial decision to revert; who knows what’s to say what would have happened if he hadn’t.</p>



<p>The last Aussie standing is a bit of exaggeration of course; not in the terms of the final sample left but even in the lineage there have been Aussie batsmen who have differed from the norm. A Mark Waugh, or going back into the mists of time, Victor Trumper, if one is to believe the raves of the past. But it’s the norm that one is interested.</p>



<p>Consider the quintessential on-the-up punch. Until Sachin Tendulkar came along, it wasn’t natural in the Indian way. Not that no one played it; of course they did. Even Ravi Shastri, usually not associated with that shot, has unfurled a few such beauties (watch his 187 against England in 1990). There is an awesome on-the-up wallop from Sunil Gavaskar in the 1983 Test series against Michael Holding; a tiny shuffle back and across, and SMG just punches it gorgeously past the non-striker. The point, as ever, is the norm; what seemed natural. With Tendulkar it was. Up on his toes, a slight shift of weight to the back, and punching good back of length balls, and at times even length deliveries, back past the bowler. It used to be a startling sight in his initial days.</p>



<p>In the decade before Tendulkar, it was the Aussies who would play it easily, naturally, smoothly. Of course it was because they grew up on tracks with bounce. The arms power that shot. The Indians tend to collapse the arms a bit, and allow the wrists to enter the scene. Aussies jabbed like boxers. Warner does it. With him, perhaps since he is a left-hander, he punches more through covers. A young Warner was a lot more feisty, pouncing on even length balls, if he was confident enough that there was no great deviation off the pitch, to punch em. Travis Head too punches but he collapses the arm, and the wrist-cock comes into the picture.</p>



<p>Warner doesn’t move his feet all that much but nearly every ball, even in defense or leaving the ball alone, there is a sense of furious kinetic energy at the crease. A side-on angle is best to view him. A furious press-back, then the opening of the front foot – he might just be defending the ball but until that moment of anaesthetising, he would make it seem as if he was about to jab.</p>



<p>It’s something he has worked on. During Mickey Arthur’s reign as coach, the focus apparently was on Warner getting his defence tighter – not a bad thing but it stripped him off the furious base he needed. It ended up anaesthetising himself somewhat, going by the quote of the coach Trent Woodhill that he worked with during that phase.</p>



<p>Woodhill told the Guardian newspaper that Warner’s first thought “was to get his defence in order and get into his innings then look to attack. To me, that defeats his natural instincts and his natural instinct is to attack and when he looks to attack, he’s in a really good defensive position because he lets balls go late, he can play late, so he plays the swinging ball later, he moves his feet. I’m not saying he’s a big mover of his feet, but he moves his body well. And when you look to defend, you naturally become really stable and stability isn’t such a good thing if it means you can’t move and react.”</p>



<p>It’s interesting that Woodhill says that as it also sides with the stereotypical Aussie batting image that resides in the head. That busyness. Consider the frenetic movements of Michael Slater, a fabulous Test opener from Australia. Seldom has anyone taken the back-and-across movement to heart as much as he did. Very busy; yet, so compact. So Australian.</p>



<p>Steve Waugh, to an extent, had that. Pressing back and across, on the move, trying to gain as much time as possible to defend. Slater would use that extra time to attack; Waugh for defense. Of course, then suddenly, he would flash his arms for that spanking cut. Not the horizontal shot necessarily, but a flamboyant fluid release of punchy arms. Ian Chappell too swore by that back-and-across movement. David Boon had a furious twirl of the bat and a fierce cut,</p>



<p>For the flamboyance in horizontal shots, Gilchrist was a good example. But he would push on where the other Aussies, traditionally, stopped. With him the extension of the arms was the key differentiator. Where most batsmen stop their arm-swing, Gilchrist’s arms would go cleanly through the line of the ball. You can only marvel at the absence of any self-doubt that allows him to play like that.What if the ball cuts away fractionally? What if it keeps slightly low or higher than what one expected? What if the length is fractionally shorter or fuller than what one thought? What if the pace is slower than anticipated? It’s as if he had no such doubts. Through his career he did the improbable – made happy both the purists and those who seek instant gratification.</p>



<p>Warner doesn’t let go of himself that way in all his shots. He curtails his punch; else it’s not a punch by definition. At times, he would be airborne when he plays that on-the-up punch.</p>



<p>Before his 100th Test, some of his team-mates were asked by Channel 7 about what they think is Warner’s trademark shot. The swivel-lap-around pull-flick he plays was picked by the likes of Josh Hazlewood; incidentally it was the shot with which he brought up his hundred; a four off Kagiso Rabada. Some like Marnus Labuschagne and Travis Head went for the square-drive. It’s a shot he has played a million times. The bowlers tend to take it across from the back of length or length and try to surprise him with the fuller one, hoping to catch him off-balance. But in his pomp, he would keep scything that ball through cover point. But we have seen the prince of that shot, regardless of the length, in Brian Lara. So, it’s the punch that’s best associated with Warner. It suits his feisty personality and the overall balance he strives to keep at crease.</p>



<p>For a long while, he would be so intent on staying side-on, that compactness allows him that balance to unreel all the off-side devilry, that the bowlers could tie him up on the leg and middle line. They still do it, go around the stumps and nail him there. Then, he would press back, almost jump back, and try to shovel it behind square to change the strike. If the bowler misses the good length and drags it back, he can collapse the arm for his short-arm pulls. Stuart Broad did the angle best, taking the ball away marginally from Warner to induce edges.</p>



<p><strong>Failure against quality spin on turners?</strong></p>



<p>That would remain an asterisk on his batting. He hasn’t been good in conditions where the ball has turned. R Ashwin has upset his most prized element at the crease – his balance, his compactness- and has troubled him. If the pitch allows for the ball to turn the width of two stumps, then Ashwin would land it outside leg. Forced to open up, Warner couldn’t cope up without the silken wrists needed to smother it. He has tried jumping out; no luck. He has tried pressing back; no luck. Perhaps because of his short height and reach, his sweeps in the subcontinent don’t have that venom-stripping effect of Matthew Hayden, who would come down hard on the ball from the top. Warner still tries to sweep bat parallel to the ground and without the necessary reach, he hasn’t always managed to get out of jail with that weapon on turners.</p>



<p>In his byte, Labuschagne had first mentioned Warner’s imperious down-the-track lofted shots to spin. Presumably, he is talking about shots on tracks that didn’t help turn.</p>



<p>The lofted shot that still sticks in the mind is the one he played during a 2012 knock of 180 against India at Perth, incidentally the innings that his father once rated as his aggressive best.</p>



<p>When long careers wind up, more often than not, the fans tend to be large-hearted, remembering the good moments more. With Warner the batsman too, that can be expected more or less. The press-backs, the ability to go airborne and still maintain balance for punches, the deliberate letting-go of the arms to slash over slips, the swivel-pulls off hips. The compactness, the arms … the last Aussie, standing.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/stuart-broad-vs-david-warner-the-last-aussie-standing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bellingham&#8217;s Salary At Real Madrid &#8216;Revealed&#8217;</title>
		<link>/bellinghams-salary-at-real-madrid-revealed/</link>
					<comments>/bellinghams-salary-at-real-madrid-revealed/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[shawon]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 18:06:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1047</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bellingham&#8217;s Salary At Real Madrid &#8216;Revealed&#8217; Jude Bellingham&#8217;s Real Madrid salary has reportedly been revealed. How much England international Jude Bellingham will earn at Real Madrid following his €103 million (R2 billion) arrival has reportedly been revealed. This week, the 14-time UEFA Champions League winners announced they had agreed to sign the 19-year-old from Borussia Dortmund, ... <a title="Bellingham&#8217;s Salary At Real Madrid &#8216;Revealed&#8217;" class="read-more" href="/bellinghams-salary-at-real-madrid-revealed/" aria-label="More on Bellingham&#8217;s Salary At Real Madrid &#8216;Revealed&#8217;">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Bellingham&#8217;s Salary At Real Madrid &#8216;Revealed&#8217;</p>



<p>Jude Bellingham&#8217;s Real Madrid salary has reportedly been revealed.</p>



<p>How much England international Jude Bellingham will earn at Real Madrid following his €103 million (R2 billion) arrival has reportedly been revealed.</p>



<p>This week, the 14-time UEFA Champions League winners announced they had agreed to sign the 19-year-old from Borussia Dortmund, beating the likes of Liverpool and Manchester City to his signature.</p>



<p>Bellingham enjoyed his most productive season in Germany this past campaign as he contributed to an impressive 21 goals in 42 matches across all competitions, with many tipping the midfielder to have a stellar career.</p>



<p>Real spent a staggering €103 million on the ex-Birmingham City starlet, but it has been reported that the Spanish giants could pay BVB an extra 30% of that fee should certain objectives be met over the course his stay in Madrid.</p>



<p>According to&nbsp;<em>AS</em>, Bellingham is set to be paid an annual figure of €20 million (R397 million) before tax on his six-year contract, which will drop to around €10 million (R198 million) after deductions.</p>



<p>This means the teenager will already be among Los Blancos&#8217; highest-paid players after the recent free-agent departures of striker Karim Benzema and winger Eden Hazard.</p>



<p>Bellingham has been given the No. 5 jersey in Spain, the shirt number famously worn by legendary Frenchman Zinedine Zidane during his spell at the club.&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/bellinghams-salary-at-real-madrid-revealed/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>When will Lionel Messi play for Inter Miami? Club schedule and potential MLS debut in July or August</title>
		<link>/when-will-lionel-messi-play-for-inter-miami-club-schedule-and-potential-mls-debut-in-july-or-august/</link>
					<comments>/when-will-lionel-messi-play-for-inter-miami-club-schedule-and-potential-mls-debut-in-july-or-august/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[shawon]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 18:02:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1044</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[When will Lionel Messi play for Inter Miami? Club schedule and potential MLS debut in July or August Lionel Messi is coming to play in the USA for Inter Miami. On on June 7, following widespread reports, with Guillem Balague first, Lionel Messi announced he has chosen to sign with Major League Soccer club Inter Miami. Messi is ... <a title="When will Lionel Messi play for Inter Miami? Club schedule and potential MLS debut in July or August" class="read-more" href="/when-will-lionel-messi-play-for-inter-miami-club-schedule-and-potential-mls-debut-in-july-or-august/" aria-label="More on When will Lionel Messi play for Inter Miami? Club schedule and potential MLS debut in July or August">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>When will Lionel Messi play for Inter Miami? Club schedule and potential MLS debut in July or August</p>



<p>Lionel Messi is coming to play in the USA for Inter Miami.</p>



<p>On on June 7, following widespread reports, with Guillem Balague first, Lionel Messi announced he has chosen to sign with Major League Soccer club Inter Miami.</p>



<p>Messi is now set to play for David Beckham&#8217;s club 16 years after Beckham signed for the LA Galaxy and changed the face of the league. It&#8217;s expected that Messi&#8217;s arrival will leave a similar impact on the league, or greater, expanding the fanbase, and transforming the way it&#8217;s perceived both domestically and around the world.</p>



<p>With Messi&#8217;s arrival now official, focus transitions to when he will take the field for the MLS club. The 2023 MLS regular season, which stretches from February to October, is currently underway. On the day of Messi&#8217;s announcement, Inter Miami sat last in the Eastern Conference table, six points away from the final playoff spot. In their first game since the announcement, Inter Miami dropped a 3-1 result against the New England Revolution.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">When will Lionel Messi debut for Inter Miami?</h2>



<p>One day prior to Messi&#8217;s official announcement, The Athletic published a report on his decision, and stated that Inter Miami boasted &#8220;growing hope&#8221; that a deal could be close, simultaneously warning that &#8220;confidence in a deal has fluctuated week to week and even day to day.&#8221;</p>



<p>The report by The Athletic included a note that should he join Inter Miami, he could potentially debut in the new Leagues Cup competition between Liga MX and MLS. Inter Miami are slated to&nbsp;<strong>play Mexico&#8217;s Cruz Azul at home on Friday, July 21</strong>&nbsp;to begin group stage play.</p>



<p>This would give Messi a month-long break following Argentina&#8217;s two summer friendlies against Australia and Indonesia on June 15 and June 19, respectively. Messi showed his form in the first friendly against the Socceroos, netting a goal in the second minute, the fastest goal in his career. Naturally, the excitement for his debut with Inter Miami will continue to build if he keeps finding the back of the net in friendlies for Argentina, not to mention dazzling displays of on-ball magic like this moment of brilliance.</p>



<p>However, the wait could potentially be slightly longer. According to Jonathan Tannenwald of the Philadelphia Inquirer, MLS sources told him that August could be a more likely debut date.</p>



<p>MLS is taking a month-long break from mid-July to mid-August for the playing of the Leagues Cup tournament, and if he waits until August, a home debut on Sunday, August 20 at against Charlotte FC could make the most sense.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Inter Miami schedule for 2023 season</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table><tbody><tr><td><strong>Date</strong></td><td><strong>Time (ET)</strong></td><td><strong>Fixture</strong></td><td><strong>Competition</strong></td></tr><tr><td>Sat, Jun. 24</td><td>7:30 p.m.</td><td>@ Philadelphia</td><td>MLS regular season</td></tr><tr><td>Sat, Jul. 1</td><td>7:30 p.m.</td><td>vs. Austin FC</td><td>MLS regular season</td></tr><tr><td>Wed, Jul. 4</td><td>7:30 p.m.</td><td>vs. Columbus Crew</td><td>MLS regular season</td></tr><tr><td>Sat, Jul. 8</td><td>7:30 p.m.</td><td>@ D.C. United</td><td>MLS regular season</td></tr><tr><td>Sat, Jul. 15</td><td>8:30 p.m.</td><td>@ St. Louis City SC</td><td>MLS regular season</td></tr><tr><td>Fri, Jul. 21</td><td>8 p.m.</td><td>vs. Cruz Azul</td><td>Leagues Cup</td></tr><tr><td>Tue, Jul. 25</td><td>7:30 p.m.</td><td>vs. Atlanta United</td><td>Leagues Cup</td></tr><tr><td>Sun, Aug. 20</td><td>7:30 p.m.</td><td>vs. Charlotte FC</td><td>MLS regular season</td></tr><tr><td>Sat, Aug. 26</td><td>7:30 p.m.</td><td>@ NY Red Bulls</td><td>MLS regular season</td></tr><tr><td>Wed, Aug. 30</td><td>7:30 p.m.</td><td>vs. Nashville SC</td><td>MLS regular season</td></tr><tr><td>Sat, Sep. 3</td><td>10:30 p.m.</td><td>@ LAFC</td><td>MLS regular season</td></tr><tr><td>Sat, Sep. 9</td><td>7:30 p.m.</td><td>vs. Sporting KC</td><td>MLS regular season</td></tr><tr><td>Sat, Sep. 16</td><td>7:30 p.m.</td><td>@ Atlanta United</td><td>MLS regular season</td></tr><tr><td>Wed, Sep. 20</td><td>7:30 p.m.</td><td>vs. Toronto FC</td><td>MLS regular season</td></tr><tr><td>Sun, Sep. 24</td><td>7:30 p.m.</td><td>@ Orlando City SC</td><td>MLS regular season</td></tr><tr><td>Sat, Sep. 30</td><td>7:30 p.m.</td><td>vs. NYCFC</td><td>MLS regular season</td></tr><tr><td>Wed, Oct. 4</td><td>8:30 p.m.</td><td>@ Chicago Fire</td><td>MLS regular season</td></tr><tr><td>Sat, Oct. 7</td><td>7:30 p.m.</td><td>vs. FC Cincinnati</td><td>MLS regular season</td></tr><tr><td>Sat, Oct. 21</td><td>6:00 p.m.</td><td>@ Charlotte FC</td><td>MLS regular season</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Why did Lionel Messi join Inter Miami?</h2>



<p>The Athletic report stated that&nbsp;Lionel Messi had ruled out a move to Saudi Arabia from his list of potential options. That left the decision down to just two clubs — his former side Barcelona, or MLS club Inter Miami.</p>



<p>Reports claimed that Messi preferred Barcelona, but there were significant uncertainties around that possibility, mostly down to the club&#8217;s murky financial situation, and whether they could even craft a contract for Messi. Reporting around Europe claimed that Barcelona were unable to offer Messi any guarantees of contract viability, and that seems to have forced his hand.</p>



<p>Major League Soccer is &#8220;getting very creative with all of this,&#8221; and has &#8220;everything is on the table&#8221; according to The Athletic, in the effort to bring Messi to the United States.</p>



<p>Playing in the United States would afford Lionel Messi with the perfect conglomeration of all the best avenues for a final playing stop before retirement. He would have ample commercial opportunities — reports claim that Apple and Adidas are intervening to help lure Messi to the U.S. It&#8217;s unclear exactly how those two MLS partners will ultimately be involved, but revenue sharing opportunities have been floated.</p>



<p>Additionally, in the United States, star athletes can still typically lead normal lives, as Beckham has often shared. That, in addition to an existing home in Miami and the proximity to Argentina where he will continue to play for the national team, and the move to Major League Soccer makes sense.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Why did Lionel Messi turn down Barcelona and Saudi Arabia?</h2>



<p>This question is much simpler to answer.</p>



<p>With Barcelona, it&#8217;s all down to the club&#8217;s financial standing. According to reports, they were simply unable to offer guarantees that they could float him a contract, and with Messi hoping to nail down his future in a timely manner, he ultimately couldn&#8217;t wait for them to figure it out.</p>



<p>The reasons behind Messi turning down Saudi Arabia are a little harder to parse out. According to reports, the Saudi league offered Messi a contract worth over $1 billion, a monetary value that is a figure that feels nearly impossible for anyone to turn down. While Messi is well-off to begin with, even someone of his net wealth would find it hard to turn his back to $1 billion.</p>



<p>Yet he did, and it&#8217;s likely down to what Messi values at this juncture in his career. Largely considered the greatest player of all-time, Messi seems to be concerned about his legacy as much as his financial standing.</p>



<p>If a report from French publication L&#8217;Equipe is to be believed, his wife Antonela Roccuzzo was also a big factor in ultimately turning down the Saudi offer. </p>



<p>The visibility of the United States is also probably important to Messi, both from a commercial standpoint and a competition standpoint, compared to the Saudi league. Messi&#8217;s performance will be highly scrutinized, much more than it would have been in Saudi Arabia, and while that comes with risks, he will likely be up for the challenge of finishing the job that Pele and Beckham started and help maximize soccer&#8217;s potential in the USA.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/when-will-lionel-messi-play-for-inter-miami-club-schedule-and-potential-mls-debut-in-july-or-august/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
